#### Contact

11592 Celine St. El Monte, CA 91732 6265378307 (Home) cwlam1987@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/wilson-lam87 (LinkedIn) www.wilsondevworks.com/ (Personal) www.wilsondevworks.com/ (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Front-end Development React.js JavaScript

### Languages

Mandarian (Elementary)

# Wilson Lam

Software Engineer at Model Match

Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

## Summary

I am a solutions-driven Full-Stack Web Developer with strong skill sets in both Front-End and Back-End. By utilizing these tools, I've built several features for Omou and created websites for local businesses.

Working for Omou has taught me that the world of coding is vast. I've learned a lot from new ways to debug, problem solving from a high level, new frameworks and libraries, etc. While working as a Teaching Assistant for my bootcamp, I've reinforced and improved upon my problem solving skills in both Front-End and Back-End. Inherently, this job also gave me experience in some soft skills like communication, patience, and translating code to English.

While attending the coding bootcamp through UCLA Extension, I gained experience in React, HTML, CSS, BootStrap for the Front-End while using Node, Express, MySQL and MongoDB for the Back-End.

My love for technology has always been present, from when I first learned how to build my own computer, reading about security vulnerabilities of gaming systems, and watching tech conventions. It is the core of my motivation and why I continually learn new topics on coding.

Page 1 of 2

### Experience

Model Match Software Engineer March 2021 - Present (2 months)

Omou Learning
Frontend Developer
February 2020 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

Self employed Full-stack Developer October 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

UCLA Extension
Teaching Assistant
September 2019 - March 2021 (1 year 7 months)
Westwood, California

Letter Ride LLC
Delivery Driver
October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)
Temple City, CA

## Education

**UCLA Extension** 

Certificate , Full Stack Web Development · (2019 - 2019)